http://visitmt.com/about-us/privacy-policy.html

Skip to main content
COVID-19 INFO & TRAVEL UPDATES:
privacy policy
Below is the privacy policy for our website visitmt.com. By visiting our website and submitting information to us, you consent to the following:
In order for you to use our website, subscribe to electronic communications, receive print publications, participate in programs or contests, we collect personal information that you submit to us. The personal information we collect is limited to the information you voluntarily provide. The information may include your name, telephone number, email address and mailing address. The information is used by us to comply with your request for information and to occasionally notify you about something you have expressed an interest in, such as an attraction, event or promotion.
This information is retained for 18 months, in compliance with state of Montana record retention policy, unless a request is made to delete the data or extend retention of the data.
This site uses YouTube and Vimeo videos. If you view any videos you are agreeing to the privacy policies of YouTube and Vimeo. You can review YouTube’s privacy policy here and Vimeo’s  here.
We also collect nonpersonal information. The nonpersonal information we collect is limited to information stored in web cookies and information derived from the IP addresses of your device (such as a computer or mobile phone). The information may be analyzed to create summary statistics, recognize trends, gather broad demographic data and personalize information for visitors to the website using customer preferences as well as a visitor’s location. The information may also be used for retargeting ads. These log files are automatically deleted after 60 days.
We may share your information with our partners and affiliates for practical and analytical reasons such as monitoring how effective our advertisements are at inspiring viewers to visit Montana. However, we will not sell your personal or nonpersonal information to a third-party, nor will we share your information with a third-party for the purpose of creating a call or mail list.
We utilize reasonable security procedures to safeguard your personal information and to protect your privacy, but we are not liable for any failure to safeguard your information.
If you would like to request, modify or delete the information you have provided us, please contact
ndwyer@mt.gov.  If you wish to opt out of cookies that allow us to serve our advertisements while you are in Montana, and collect aggregate information on arrivals, click here.
Change or revoke your cookie consent
